biggreenegg.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy - Big Green Egg - The Ultimate Cooking Experience | Big Green Egg - The Ultimate Cooking Experience

**Privacy Policy**

Visitors to the Big Green Egg web site are not required to register or purchase any products.

Big Green Egg, Inc. (BGE) is sensitive to concerns about user information. By entering user information on the BGE Website, you consent to our use of such information for purposes that are described herein. You may also provide us with personal information as required for BGE to provide you with services relating to products that you purchase from us, such as Warranty Registration for a Big Green Egg.

**Disclosure of Information**

BGE does not sell, rent or share personal information with any unaffiliated third party, except as may be necessary to provide our services.

We have chosen a third party to process our credit card transactions in order to provide enhanced security, reliability and fraud protection mechanisms for your purchases. The credit card information that you choose to provide during your purchase is maintained in the credit card processing company’s database for accounting and billing purposes. Unless expressly authorized by you, we do not maintain a copy of your credit card information on our servers.

Under certain situations, we may disclose information collected from the Website (i) if required or permitted pursuant to any applicable law, regulation, or court or administrative order; (ii) in connection with any user’s violation of posted terms of use for the Website or other agreements with BGE; (iii) to protect the property of BGE or its affiliates; or (iv) to protect the personal safety of employees of BGE or its affiliates, other users of the Website or a member of the public.

Without limiting the foregoing, by giving us user information you are giving us permission to provide you with promotional and/or other marketing information about BGE products, services and offerings. If you elect to receive such promotional and/or marketing information, you may opt-out of receiving such materials by following the opt-out instructions contained in the materials or by emailing BGE at opt-out@BigGreenEgg.com.

**Children’s Privacy**

We do not intend to collect information from children. If we discover that the Website has inadvertently collected information from a child, we will promptly take all reasonable measures to delete that data.

**Security**

This Website uses industry-standard security measures to protect certain user information. When our site asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is protected with encryption software such as Secure Sockets Layer – SSL. Unfortunately, no data transmitted over or accessible through the public Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we attempt to protect a user’s personally identifiable information, BGE cannot ensure or warrant that any user information will be completely secure from misappropriation by hackers or from other nefarious or criminal activities, or in the event of a failure of computer hardware, software, or a telecommunications network. This Website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that BGE is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites – please review those site’s privacy policy statement.

**Cookies**

BGE uses computer cookies to store information to help analyze what is happening on our site so we can improve the functionality. Our cookies do not contain financial or personally identifiable information. BGE does not correlate the cookie information with data about individual users, nor does it share this information or sell it to any third party. If you prefer not to receive cookies from this Website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. Please know that certain features of this Website may be unavailable if your browser is not set to support or enable cookies.

**Policy Updates**

We review this privacy policy at regular intervals for compliance with internal procedures and industry standards. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. If we change this privacy policy, we will post the changes on the Privacy Policy link on our web site. We encourage you to check our website frequently for updates.

**Contact Information**

If you would like to contact us with questions or comments concerning the accuracy and/or privacy of your information please notify us by contacting the following:

Big Green Egg, Inc.

3786 DeKalb Technology Parkway

Atlanta, GA 30340 USA

e-mail: online@BigGreenEgg.com  
telephone 770.938.9394

We welcome your questions and comments.

**Website Information**

All information and product specifications contained on the Big Green Egg website are subject to change without notice, and BGE reserves the right to modify such information at any time.
